第一节，听下。
面五段对话，每段对话后有一个小题，从题中所给的
三个选项中选出最佳选项，并标在试卷的相应位置。
听完每段对话后，你都有十秒钟的时间来回答。
有关小题和阅读下一小题，
每段对话仅读一遍。
现在你有五秒钟的时间阅读第一小题的有关内容
,Stewart! It's nice to see you here.
Are you also looking for the book for our science class?
No, not really.
I want to buy a storybook.
Mary, I'm sorry.
I can't pick you up at the airport this afternoon.
I have to visit an important customer.
That's okay. I can go home by taxi.
Thank you, dear.
I'll be home early, and let's eat out tonight.
Dr. Anderson's office.
May I help you?
I'd like to have Dr.
Anderson examine my teeth.
Can I come tomorrow?
Let me see.
I'm afraid Dr.
Anderson won't be able to see you tomorrow.
What about Thursday, then?
Excuse me, could you show me the way to the cinema, please?
Sorry, but I'm a here myself.
Jane, why are you here in the office?
I thought you were leaving for New York today.
Yes, but my flight is not until this evening.
see. Then I can give you a ride to the airport after work.
Thank you, Kevin.
That's very nice of you.
第一节到此。
此结束。
第二节，听下面五段对话或独白，每段对话或独白后有二至四个小题，从
题中所给的
三个选项中选出最佳选项，并标在试。
院的相应位置。
听每段对话或独白前，你将有五秒钟的时间阅读各个小题。
听完后，各小题将给出五秒钟的作答时间。
每段对话或独白读两遍。
听下面一段对话，回答第六和第七题。
现在你有十秒钟的时间阅读这两个小题。
Excuse me, I'm lost.
How do I get to the market?
You're a bit far from there.
I hope you are not in hurry.
No, I just need to buy some food.
Which way should I go?
Go straight the following blocks, then turn left and walk about two blocks.
The market is on the right side of the street.
You can take a bus at the next crossroads.
How long does it take if I walk there?
Around 30 minutes.
That's not far away.
Thank you. Excuse me, I'm lost.
How do I get to the market?
You're a bit far from there.
I hope you are not in a hurry.
No, I just need to buy some food.
Which way should I go?
Go straight the following blocks, then turn left and walk about two blocks.
The market is on the right side of the street.
You can take a bus at the next crossroads.
How long does it take if I walk there?
Around 30 minutes.
That's not far away.
Thank you. David, have you heard the news?
听下面一段对话，回答第八。
质地十题。
现在你有十五秒钟的时间阅读这三个小题。
Our school team is in the finals.
I know. I watched the match on TV last night.
Do you think they were good?
They certainly were.
A group of us have decided to go and support them in the finals.
Will you come along too?
I'm not sure.
When is it?
It's on Saturday afternoon at 3.30 and we'll get at the school gate at 3 o So, are
you coming? No, I don't think so.
I've got piano lessons at 2.30 every Saturday.
Can't you have it on another day?
But my mother really likes it.
Come on, Lisa.
This is the finals.
Our school team has been working hard and they need our support.
Well, let me talk with my mom first, okay?
Once you have made a decision, just give me a call.
David, have you heard the news?
Our school team is in the finals.
I know. I watched the match on TV last night.
Do you think they were good?
They certainly were.
A group of us have decided to go and support them in the finals.
Will you come along too?
I'm not sure.
When is it?
It's on Saturday afternoon at 3.30 and we'll get at the school gate at 3 o So, are
you coming? No, I don't think so.
I've got piano lessons at 2.30 every Saturday.
Can't you have it on another day?
But my mother really likes it.
Come on, Lisa.
This is the finals.
Our school team has been working hard and they need our support.
Well, let me talk with my mom first, okay?
Once you have made a decision, just give me a call.
听下面一段对话，回答第十一。
这第十三题，现在你有十五秒钟的时间阅读这三个小题。
Oh, that's the second bus that has gone on my phone.
I wonder where all the people come from.
I really think they should let more people on at this time of the day when there's
so many people going to work.
But they won't allow people to stand on the bus.
You know, too dangerous.
I don't mind that.
Look. I think that is an 11, isn't it?
No, I'm afraid not.
It's 17. I think I'll go by underground tomorrow.
No, not me.
I can't stand all stuck in standing.
Besides, I need to look at the scenery.
I see what you mean.
Oh, here comes a number of them.
Two, no, three.
Anyway, we are sure to get on one of them.
Oh, that's the second bus that has gone on my phone.
I wonder where all the people come from.
I really think they should let more people on at this time of the day when there's
so many people going to work.
But they won't allow people to stand on the bus.
You know, too dangerous.
I don't mind that.
Look. I think that is an 11, isn't it?
No, I'm afraid not.
It's 17. I think I'll go by underground tomorrow.
No, not me.
I can't stand all stuck in standing.
Besides, I need to look at the scenery.
I see what you mean.
Oh, here comes a number of them.
Two, no, three.
Anyway, we are sure to get on one of them.
听下面一段对话，回答第十。
四至第十六题。
现在你有十五秒钟的时间阅读这三个小题。
Hi, my name is Anne Smith.
Hi, I'm Bill Harrington.
Harrington, I need to ask you a few questions before I show you what we have.
First, what price can you accept?
Somewhere between 800 and 900 rent a month.
Okay, did you have a particular place in mind?
Well, I would like to live somewhere near the university, or at least on the bus
line. I have a class to attend early in the morning.
Okay, are there any other things you would like to have?
For example, a dishwasher, a swimming pool, or an air conditioner?
I would certainly like to a dishwasher,
and something more like this air conditioning would be necessary.
Oh, yes, and two bedrooms will be nice.
Okay, here are photos of the flats that meet your requirements.
Thank you, this one past the street looks nice.
I would like to see it, and the one on Main Street.
Sure, let me get the keys and we can go right away.
Great, thank you.
Hi, my name is Anne Smith.
Hi, I'm Bill Harrington.
Mr. Harrington, I need to ask you a few questions before I show you what we have.
First, what price can you accept?
Well, would like to live somewhere near the university, or at least on the bus line.
I have a class to attend early in the morning.
Okay, are there any other things you would like to have?
For example, a dishwasher, a swimming pool,
I would certainly like to a dishwasher, and something more like this air
conditioning would be necessary.
Oh, yes, and two bedrooms will be nice.
Okay, here are photos of the flats that meet your requirements.
Thank you, this one past the street looks nice.
I would like to see it, and the one on Main Street.
Sure, let me get the keys and we can go right away.
Great, thank you.
听下面一段独白，回答第十七至第二十题。
现在你有二十秒钟的时间阅读这四个小题。
Hi, everybody. Welcome to the SeaLife Center.
This is an extremely exciting place with so many things to see.
It costs four pounds with grownups, and two pounds for children.
It opens at 8.30 a.m.
every day of the year, except the 25th and 26th of December, when the center is
closed. Special attractions to the children include the hourly feeding times for all
the different fish.
Starting at 9.30 a.m., you can see everything here from the biggest fish to the
smallest. Every morning from 10 o there are short films for children in the SeaLife
Theater. Someone is always there to answer questions about what she's seen.
The latest attraction of the center is a big glass passage you can walk through all
around you. You'll see fish swimming sometimes even over your head.
You certainly have a fierce possible view of the underwater world children like.
It's really amazing for grownups too.
I'm sure you have a good time here.
Hi everybody. Welcome to the SeaLife Center.
This is an extremely exciting place with so many things to see.
It costs four pounds with grownups, and two pounds for children.
It opens at 8.30 a.m.
every day of the year, except the 25th and 26th of December, when the center is
closed. Special attractions to the children include the hourly feeding times for all
the different fish.
Starting at 9.30 a.m., you can see everything here from the biggest fish to the
smallest. Every morning from 10 o there are short films for children in the SeaLife
Theater. Someone is always there to answer questions about what she's seen.
The latest attraction of the center is a big glass passage you can walk through all
around you. You'll see fish swimming sometimes even over your head.
You certainly have a fierce possible view of the underwater world children like.
It's really amazing for grownups too.
I'm sure you have a good time here.
The Thank you for watching.
第二节到此结束。
现在你有两分钟的时间，将试卷上的答案转涂到客观题答题卡上。
涨。
you you you Thank for watching.
听力部分到此结束。
you